us-mattress.com 2017-09-06

# US-Mattress Privacy Policy

| 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 **Privacy Statement for US-Mattress:**  
Bedding Pros LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.us-mattress.com, which is owned and operated by Bedding Pros LLC. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. We do not link IP address/ log files to personally identifiable information. This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are clicking to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

Bedding Pros LLC, through its website www.us-mattress.com, collects your personal order information for processing your payments and arranging your order delivery. Your credit card information is shared back with the credit card company for making payment. Of course, we also then provide your address and contact information to our shipping companies in order for them to make the delivery. Bedding Pros LLC, maintains this privacy standard. The website is hosted by Yahoo, which does not own or use personal information you provide when placing orders. The order information you enter is collected by Yahoo and then transmitted back to Bedding Pros LLC. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to purchase products. We collect visitors contact information (like their email address, phone number and address) and financial information (like their credit card number). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.   
Your information will be used to contact you regarding your order, payment and delivery. We may occasionally send you information through other companies (BuySafe, MyBuys, etc) on products, special deals & promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us any time on any page in the site. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. We will not sell your information to anyone. If you wish to change or update personal information previously provided to our site, please email us at custserv@us-mattress.com with your changes and we will update our records. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Order information is received via SSL encryption protected lines. Received information is stored on secure computers, or in paper invoice form, in locked locations. Your information is only available to user ID authorized employees with electronic access. Hard copy information such, as invoices, is only available to employees directly involved in processing your order. Our site under goes an annual security assessment, and all employees are routinely counseled to maintain strict information controls. We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site. 

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com). 

This website uses the first-party Google Analytics cookie only to track your return visits but not to identify you personally by name, email, or any other data. This site also uses the third-party DoubleClick cookie to enable reporting on demographics and interests information (such as age, gender, and favored product categories), but again, not in any way that is associated with personally identifiable information. If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. For more information on Google Analytics, please visit <http://www.google.com/analytics/>. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

Attn: Privacy Manager   
Bedding Pros LLC  
35799 Industrial Road  
Livonia, MI 48150  

 **Personal Protection Policy:**  
Your personal protection is a priority at US-Mattress.com. Accordingly, your orders are processed with powerful encryption technology to achieve maximum information protection. Federal law limits your liability to $50 for fraudulent use of your credit card. US-Mattress will cover your liability up to $50 in the unlikely event your purchase transaction on our site results in fraudulent use of your card. Furthermore, US-Mattress.com will not sell or share your personal information to outside parties. Period. We are delighted you visited our store. If we can be of any further service, please drop us an email for a prompt reply. Please enjoy your shopping experience. We know you will!

|  Free Delivery  
Your Comfort Guaranteed
